laptopunderbudget.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy - Laptop Under Budget

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

## What information do we collect from the people that visit our website?

We collect name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you sign up for our newsletter,  get expert advise (feature), surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.

### How do we protect your information?

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

## Do we use ‘cookies’?

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

## Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

### Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy.

### According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

  * Users can visit our site anonymously.
  * Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.
  * Users are able to change their personal information by emailing us.

## COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

#### We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
  * NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at  
[contact@laptopunderbudget.com](mailto:contact@laptopunderbudget.com) and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

## Contacting Us –

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

**Postal Address –**  
548, Market St.  
San Francisco, California 94104  
United States.
